export const quizData = [
	{
		question: 'What is binding post usually made of?',
		answers: ['Stainless steel', 'Aluminum', 'Brass or bronze', 'Copper'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the binding post the electrical contact for?',
		answers: [
			'The power cord and switch',
			'The armature bar and coils',
			'The soldering lugs and to the contact screw',
			'The capacitor and rear spring'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What does the binding post hold?',
		answers: ['Rear spring', 'Contact screw', 'Armature bar', 'Tube vise'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the binding post a positive contact for?',
		answers: ['The foot switch', 'The grip', 'The power', 'The capacitor'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'How many years after renewing your license do you have to complete your continuing education?',
		answers: ['2 years', '1 year', '4 years', '3 years'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the yoke.',
		answers: [
			'A coil alignment tool',
			'The foot switch connector',
			'A metal frame that holds the machine together. And Regulates the height of the coils',
			'The spring stabilizer'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is another name for the tube vise on coil machine?',
		answers: ['Retainer', 'Cruncher/crusher', 'Lock bolt', 'Vice clamp'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the Oring?',
		answers: [
			'A washer to reduce coil noise',
			'Used to minimize the vibration of the machine and give it a smoother run. It is placed tightly under the spring and pulled back over the cap screw.',
			'A plastic ring inside the clip cord',
			'A spring stiffener'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'Rear spring',
		answers: [
			'Plastic. Controls grip rotation.',
			'Brass. Supports tube grip.',
			'Steel. Controls the downward force of the machine. A thinner spring means that the machine moves with less force, where a thicker gauge spring runs with greater force.',
			'Rubber. Insulates rear contact.'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'Front Spring:',
		answers: [
			'Brass, low tension, absorbs vibration',
			"Steel, low angle, Converts a tattoo machine's coils into an electromagnet and acts as a shock absorber for the armature bar",
			'Copper, high tension, increases throw',
			'Aluminum, flat, adjusts speed'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'Contact screw is best made out of',
		answers: ['Brass', 'Iron', 'Stainless steel', 'Aluminum'],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'Must the contact screw be smooth',
		answers: ['True'],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What causes the A-BAr to rattle:',
		answers: [
			'Inconsistent voltage',
			'Weak capacitor',
			'When the gap is too small it will cause the a-bar to bounce off of the rear coil and incorrectly hit the front coil, if there is debris present, if screws do not fit correctly. if the front spring hangs over the armature bar',
			'Low quality ink'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What can cause a machine to run hot?',
		answers: [
			'Old rubber bands',
			'Frayed clip cord',
			'Coils with too much core showing',
			'Loose armature bar'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What can a lower contact spring angle do?',
		answers: [
			'Reduces noise',
			'Improves shading',
			'Allows your machine to run at lower voltage',
			'Increases throw distance'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'Back spring should be?',
		answers: [
			'60 on the Rockwell scale',
			'48 on the Rockwell scale',
			'51 on the Rockwell scale',
			'36 on the Rockwell scale'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What can dampen vibration?',
		answers: [
			'Rubber grommets',
			'Plastic washers',
			'Bronze washers or double up on them',
			'Spring dampeners'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the Needle Bar',
		answers: [
			'Moves the coils',
			'Holds the needle in place and drives the needle down.',
			'Adjusts the armature bar gap',
			'Grounds the contact screw'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is true about the a-bar',
		answers: [
			'Should be chrome-plated for conductivity',
			'Made of brass for flexibility',
			'Should be plain steel. should hit flat on the coil core',
			'Made of carbon fiber'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What does the frame act as?',
		answers: [
			'A spring holder',
			'The structural clamp',
			'Acts as a ground for the coil circuit',
			'The ink stabilizer'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What are the coils?',
		answers: [
			'1.25 inches tall, 5/16-3/8 diameter. turns into a magnet when electricity is introduced',
			'Magnet holders inside the needle bar',
			'Carbon fiber rods that move ink',
			'2-inch solid steel rods that hold contact screws'
		],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},

	// {
	// 	question: 'Skin lesions are classified as either primary or secondary. What is the difference',
	// 	answers: [
	// 		'Primary are internal; secondary are external',
	// 		'Primary is lesions that first appear. Secondary are results of changes to the primary lesions brought on by manipulation(i.e. Scratching or rubbing)',
	// 		'Primary are painless; secondary are painful',
	// 		'Primary come from allergies; secondary come from trauma'
	// 	],
	// 	correctAnswer: 1
	// },
	{
		question: 'What agency does high level disinfect have to be registered with',
		answers: ['FDA', 'CDC', 'OSHA', 'EPA'],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question: 'What does OHA stand for?',
		answers: [
			'Office of Health Accreditation',
			'Oregon Health Authority',
			'Oregon Hygienists Association',
			'Office of Hazardous Agents'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What agency is responsible for the safety of the inks/pigments tattoo artists use?',
		answers: ['FDA (Food and Drug Administration)', 'CDC', 'OSHA', 'EPA'],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What does the Rockwell Hardness Scale test measure?',
		answers: [
			'Magnetic resistance',
			'Heat resistance',
			'The strength of steel',
			'Electrical conductivity'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What does the steam sterilization integrator measure?',
		answers: [
			'Moisture level, ink density, bacteria growth',
			'Time, temperature, and presence of steam during the sterilization cycle',
			'Pressure, humidity, sterilizer weight',
			'Air flow, time, pH levels'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question:
			'When is the expiration date for sterilized instruments, after the initial date of sterilization?',
		answers: [
			'One year from the date of sterilization unless the package is compromised',
			'30 days from the sterilization date',
			'6 months with weekly spore testing',
			'3 years in climate-controlled storage'
		],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'How long do you need to keep spore test results?',
		answers: ['6 months', '1 year', '2 years', '5 years'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'When do integrator strips need to be used?',
		answers: [
			'Every month',
			'Only with metal tools',
			'In every cycle ran through the autoclave',
			'After failed spore test'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What word means to destroy disease germs?',
		answers: ['Antiseptic', 'Sanitize', 'Disinfect', 'Scrub'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'All wounds should be _____ and kept slightly ______ during healing.',
		answers: ['dry and exposed', 'sterile and hot', 'clean and moist', 'bandaged and airtight'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'How long is a term that is served by a member of the Board of Electrologists and Body Art Practitioners?',
		answers: ['2 years', '5 years', '3 years', '4 years'],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question:
			'How many consecutive terms can a member of the Board of Electrologists and Body Art Practitioners serve?',
		answers: ['1 year', '3 years', '2 years', '4 years'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},

	{
		question: 'What can cause your machine to rattle and deflect on the rear coil?',
		answers: [
			'Loose rubber bands',
			'Poor alignment of springs',
			'Dust, lint, and/or debris',
			'Over-lubrication'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'How often should you clean the contact area on your tattoo machine?',
		answers: ['Once a week', 'Twice a day', 'Before every tattoo', 'Once a day'],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question: 'What is true of ferrous metals',
		answers: [
			'They are primarily composed of aluminum',
			'They cannot conduct electricity',
			'Ferrous metals are materials containing iron as their primary component, such as steel and cast iron.',
			'They are naturally non-magnetic'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What should you clean the contact area with?',
		answers: ['Soap and water', 'Bleach', 'Alcohol', 'Hydrogen peroxide'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What should armature bars be made of?',
		answers: ['Aluminum', 'Bronze', 'Stainless steel', 'Plain steel'],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question: 'What is an open sore on the skin caused by the destruction of surface tissue?',
		answers: ['Pustule', 'Ulcer', 'Macule', 'Erosion'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is a common disease in which the skin loses pigment due to the destruction of pigment cells?',
		answers: ['Psoriasis', 'Melasma', 'Vitiligo', 'Dermatitis'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'If you move to a new residential address or change any of your information, how long do you have to notify the Health Licensing Office of the change?',
		answers: ['60 days', '30 days', '10 days', '90 days'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'How do you notify the HLO?',
		answers: ['Phone call or text', 'In-person visit', 'Writing or email', 'Fax only'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'Is continuing education required even if your license is inactive?',
		answers: ['Only after five years', 'Yes', 'No', 'Only for electrologists'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'How should all substances be dispensed?',
		answers: [
			'Must be dispensed into a single use container and discarded at the end of each procedure',
			'From large containers to save cost',
			'In reusable glass containers',
			'Directly from the manufacturer’s bottle'
		],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'How many people are on the Board of Electrologists and Body Art Practitioners?',
		answers: ['5', '9', '7', '6'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'When a service is completed, what type of waste receptacle must the regulated waste be put into?',
		answers: [
			'A biohazard bag inside a covered container',
			'Any available trash bin',
			'A cloth-lined laundry bin',
			'All service-related waste must be enclosed in a glove or bag and disposed of in a covered container with a biohazard label that has a garbage liner'
		],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question: 'Ensure all ________ are kept at adequate strengths to maintain effectiveness.',
		answers: ['antiseptics', 'disinfecting solutions', 'chemicals', 'detergents'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'When storing chemicals in the facility, how must this be done',
		answers: [
			'In labeled and closed containers',
			'In plastic containers',
			'In unlocked drawers',
			'On open shelving'
		],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What must be clearly marked on all tattoo inks, pigments, and dyes by law?',
		answers: ['Manufacturer’s address', 'Date of mixing', 'Expiration date', 'Batch number'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is a chemical agent, registered with the EPA, which has demonstrated tuberculocidal activity?',
		answers: [
			'Mild antiseptic',
			'Low level disinfectant',
			'High level disinfectant',
			'Neutral pH soap'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a scar?',
		answers: [
			'A loss of pigment due to epidermal damage',
			'An area of fibrous tissue left behind on the skin after damaged tissue has healed',
			'A collection of fluid beneath the skin surface',
			'A small hardened lesion that results from clogged pores'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a papule?',
		answers: [
			'A cluster of small blood vessels under the skin',
			'A patch of discolored skin that does not rise above the surface',
			'A small, solid slightly raised area of the skin less than half an inch in diameter',
			'A blister filled with serous fluid'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is a small pus-containing skin blister found on skin that may or may not be caused by infection?',
		answers: ['Vesicle', 'Macule', 'Pustule', 'Ulcer'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is a group of disorders characterized by purplish or reddish brown area of discoloration, visible through the skin and caused by bleeding within the underlying tissue?',
		answers: ['Purpura', 'Petechiae', 'Lichen planus', 'Psoriasis'],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the definition of keratinization?',
		answers: [
			'The hardening of skin due to calcium buildup',
			'The process by which cells become tough and horny due to deposits of keratin placed within them',
			'The regeneration of dermal collagen',
			'The breakdown of elastin in the epidermis'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a keloid?',
		answers: [
			'A ruptured hair follicle',
			'A bacterial abscess',
			'A large permanent and sometimes disfiguring scar that may develop after surgery or other injury to the skin',
			'A benign epidermal cyst'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: "When the skin isn't pulled tight or taut, the needles in the machine can do what?",
		answers: [
			'Create inconsistent line work due to drag',
			'The needles can get caught in the skin or even bounce off it without penetrating and leaving any ink behind',
			'Cause excessive scarring from friction',
			'Inject ink too deeply causing blowout'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'How often does this quiz say you should refill your ink?',
		answers: ['Every 30 seconds', 'Every 2 minutes', 'Every 15 seconds lol', 'Every 5 minutes'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'When packing in solid color, what technique should be used?',
		answers: [
			'Light tapping in even rows',
			'Small, barely overlapping circles to fill in the appropriate areas of the tattoo',
			'Back-and-forth horizontal shading',
			'Needle dragging in one motion'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question:
			'What does the tattoo artist use to mark the skin if free handing the design according to this out of date text?',
		answers: [
			'Alcohol-based pen',
			'Single use skin scribe. (They emphasize that it is non-toxic)',
			'Carbon pencil',
			'Disinfected reusable marker'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question:
			'What should the tattoo artist do regularly to guarantee the coverage is full and even when packing color?',
		answers: [
			'Refill the ink cup after every pass',
			'Wipe away the excess ink to be able to see the coverage underneath',
			'Change needle configuration',
			'Use higher voltage for darker areas'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the largest organ of the body?',
		answers: ['Skin', 'Brain', 'Liver', 'Heart'],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the most important function of the skin?',
		answers: ['Moisture retention', 'Sensory reception', 'Protection', 'Temperature regulation'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What percent of body weight does the blood take up on average?',
		answers: ['5%', '8%', '12%', '15%'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a cyst?',
		answers: [
			'A large blood-filled swelling',
			'A closed cavity or sac containing a liquid or semisolid material beneath the skin',
			'A whitehead caused by clogged pores',
			'A hard fibrous bump near a joint'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'A crack in the skin that penetrates the dermis',
		answers: ['Fissure', 'Lesion', 'Laceration', 'Abrasion'],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What is follicular hyperkeratosis?',
		answers: [
			'Excessive hair growth due to hormone imbalance',
			'A disorder of keratinization characterized by the thickening of skin around and/or on hair follicles',
			'A form of eczema affecting follicles',
			'Overproduction of sebum in hair follicles'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: "What do Merkel's disks detect?",
		answers: ['Heat', 'Touch', 'Pain', 'Light'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What causes a callus?',
		answers: [
			'Infection from bacteria in the epidermis',
			'hyperkeratosis',
			'Accumulated sweat',
			'Allergic reaction to friction'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'Albinism',
		answers: [
			'A breakdown of collagen under the skin',
			'A vascular condition that leads to redness in skin',
			'the inability to make melanin',
			'Overproduction of melanin in patches'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: "What percentage of the body's weight does the skin account for?",
		answers: ['10%', '20%', '15%', '5%'],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What are the two main ingredients in tattoo ink?',
		answers: [
			'The pigment (color) and the carrier fluid',
			'Water and isopropyl alcohol',
			'Saline and dye',
			'Alcohol and pigment'
		],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'The majority of traditional coil machines fall into what coil count categories?',
		answers: [
			'6-coil, 9-coil, and 11-coil',
			'9-coil, 11-coil, and 13-coil',
			'8-coil, 10-coil, and 12-coil',
			'7-coil, 10-coil, and 14-coil'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What does the capacitor do on a tattoo machine?',
		answers: [
			'Regulates foot pedal responsiveness',
			'Maintains a consistent electrical charge to the machine',
			'Converts AC current to DC current',
			'Increases magnetic pull of the coils'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question:
			'When setting up a traditional tattoo machine, why does a tattoo artist put rubber bands on during the setup?',
		answers: [
			'To improve grip on the machine frame',
			'To hold the contact screw in place',
			'To apply tension on the needle bar and stabilize it',
			'To tighten the coil position against the yoke'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is folliculitis?',
		answers: [
			'Inflammation of the sebaceous gland',
			'Infection of a clogged sweat pore',
			'Inflammation of the hair follicle',
			'Chronic dry patch on the dermis'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is impetigo?',
		answers: [
			'Deep tissue staph infection common in adults',
			'Chronic allergic dermatitis affecting children',
			'Superficial skin infection caused by streptococcal or staphylococcal bacteria',
			'Viral rash associated with nerve inflammation'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What are large permanent scars that develop after injury to the skin?',
		answers: ['Papules', 'Keloids', 'Nodules', 'Keratoses'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is keratin?',
		answers: [
			'A pigment that gives skin its color',
			'A hormone that regulates oil production',
			'A sulfur-rich protein found in the outer skin, hair, and nails',
			'A lipid that protects the dermis'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is a common benign tumor that is composed of mature fat cells that almost never become malignant called?',
		answers: ['Melanoma', 'Lipoma', 'Fibrosarcoma', 'Basal cell tumor'],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a macule?',
		answers: [
			'A thickened callus caused by friction',
			'A small fluid-filled blister',
			'A flat spot on the skin, different in color and under 2 cm',
			'A raised lesion caused by embedded bacteria'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	// {
	// 	question: 'What causes our skin to detect pain?',
	// 	answers: ['Meissner’s corpuscles', 'Free nerve endings', 'Pacinian corpuscles', 'Merkel cells'],
	// 	correctAnswer: 1
	// },
	{
		question: 'What is one way a cyst of the skin can form?',
		answers: [
			'A blocked duct from a fluid-forming sebaceous gland',
			'Improper tattoo ink injection',
			'Blood pooling under the skin surface',
			'Fungal buildup in the dermis'
		],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question:
			'The contacts on the traditional tattoo machine allow what to happen when the machine is powered on?',
		answers: [
			'They amplify the magnetic field in the coils',
			'They provide grounding for the machine',
			'They complete the electrical current',
			'They convert voltage levels automatically'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the soldering lug for?',
		answers: [
			'To insulate the coil leads from the frame',
			'To stabilize the armature bar',
			'To provide a secure connection point for wires',
			'To align the contact screw for better current flow'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the medical term for a bruise?',
		answers: ['Ecchymosis', 'Papule', 'Hemangioma', 'Keratosis'],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What is dermatofibroma?',
		answers: [
			'A benign tumor, a nodule, arising from connective tissue cells',
			'A cancerous growth arising from skin cells',
			'An infection caused by a bacterial pathogen',
			'A cyst formed by trapped hair follicles'
		],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What is dermatitis?',
		answers: [
			'A fungal infection causing redness and scaling of the skin',
			'A viral infection leading to blistering and swelling',
			'A group of inflammatory conditions of the skin',
			'A condition resulting from an allergic reaction causing hives'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a cyst?',
		answers: [
			'A growth of excess tissue forming a solid mass beneath the skin',
			'A closed cavity or sac containing a liquid or semisolid material beneath the skin',
			'A bacterial infection causing inflammation and pus buildup',
			'A fluid-filled sac forming on the surface of the skin'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What causes 95% of all cases of basal cell carcinoma?',
		answers: [
			'Exposure to harsh chemicals',
			'Frequent use of tanning beds',
			'Overexposure to sunlight',
			'Genetic mutations in skin cells'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What type of skin is more likely to be diagnosed with skin cancer?',
		answers: [
			'Dark skin with dark hair',
			'Fair skin with light hair',
			'Oily skin with large pores',
			'Skin that tans easily without burning'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	// {
	// 	question: 'What are the two major components of whole blood?',
	// 	answers: [
	// 		'Plasma and cells',
	// 		'Platelets and white blood cells',
	// 		'Red blood cells and hemoglobin',
	// 		'Plasma and hormones'
	// 	],
	// 	correctAnswer: 0
	// },
	{
		question: 'What is sebum?',
		answers: [
			'A mixture of enzymes and acids that help break down food particles on the skin',
			'Consists primarily of lipids and oils to keep the hair supple and the skin soft and pliant, while preventing water loss from the epidermis',
			'A protein-based substance that helps to repair damaged skin cells',
			'A thick mucus produced to protect the skin from harmful pathogens'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'How does the body regulate its temperature?',
		answers: [
			'The skin produces heat through muscle contractions and maintains it by increasing blood flow',
			'The skin allows the body to lose heat by evaporation, radiation, convection, and conduction',
			'The body regulates temperature by secreting hormones that increase metabolic rate',
			'The body uses its internal organs to produce heat, and the skin only aids in insulation'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	// {
	// 	question: 'What is melanin?',
	// 	answers: [
	// 		'A protein that helps in the formation of collagen and elastin in the skin',
	// 		'The dark pigment formed by melanocytes; it imparts color to the skin and hair',
	// 		'An enzyme responsible for the breakdown of dead skin cells',
	// 		'A hormone that regulates the production of sweat in sweat glands'
	// 	],
	// 	correctAnswer: 1
	// },
	{
		question: 'In what order are 3 major skin groups (outermost layer first)?',
		answers: [
			'Epidermis, subcutaneous tissue, dermis',
			'Dermis, epidermis, subcutaneous tissue',
			'Epidermis, dermis, subcutaneous tissue',
			'Subcutaneous tissue, dermis, epidermis'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a sebaceous gland?',
		answers: [
			'A gland that primarily produces sweat for thermoregulation',
			'A gland that secretes mucus to moisten and protect the epithelial lining',
			'A gland that releases enzymes for breaking down dead skin cells',
			'A gland that produces sebum (protective oil for skin)'
		],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a sudoriferous gland?',
		answers: [
			'Oil-producing gland located near the hair follicle',
			'Sweat gland',
			'Sensory receptor that detects pressure changes',
			'Muscle fiber that causes hair to stand upright'
		],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question: 'What does the arrector pili muscle do?',
		answers: [
			'It regulates sweat gland activity during thermoregulation',
			'It controls the dilation of blood vessels near the skin surface',
			'This muscle can contract and cause the hair to become more perpendicular to the skin surface, also known as goose bumps',
			'It moves sebum from sebaceous glands to the outer layer of the skin'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question: 'What are the top 5 layers of skin?',
		answers: [
			'Stratum corneum, stratum lucidum, stratum granulosum, stratum spinosum, stratum basale',
			'Stratum dentine, stratum lucidum, stratum reticulare, stratum granulosum, stratum basale',
			'Stratum corneum, stratum lucidum, stratum granulosum, stratum papillare, stratum basale',
			'Stratum dentine, stratum granulosum, stratum reticulare, stratum papillare, stratum corpus'
		],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question: 'What is a mucous membrane?',
		answers: [
			'Tissue that covers bones and provides attachment points for muscles',
			'Tissue that lines blood vessels and regulates blood flow',
			'Tissue lining the surfaces of passageways leading to the outside of the body',
			'Tissue that forms the inner layer of the epidermis'
		],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which of the following best describes the composition and function of the nervous system?',
		answers: [
			'A network of connective tissues responsible for structural support and voluntary movement coordination',
			'Specialized epithelial cells that create barriers and regulate nutrient absorption across neural pathways',
			'Muscle fibers that generate electrical impulses and contract in response to neurotransmitters',
			'Cells adapted to transmit signals, respond to stimuli, and regulate both voluntary and involuntary activities'
		],
		correctAnswer: 3
	}
];
